Faculty of Education fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Program area files, 1968 - 1997; F-233-5; 2.75 m of textual records 31 photographs 1 sound recording; General note: 31 photographs located in F-233-5-1-1-84; sound recording (2 audio cassettes) related to file F-233-5-1-1-81.
  - Professional Programs files, 1968 - 1997; F-233-5-1; 2.75 m of textual records 31 photographs 1 sound recording; Physical description: includes 2 audio cassettes (located in sub-sub-series 1). General note: photographs and sound recordings are located in sub-sub-series 1.; Faculty of Education. 
    - Director's subject files, 1968 - 1997; F-233-5-1-1; 1.24 m of textual records 31 photographs 1 sound recording; Physical description: includes 2 audio cassettes (related to file 81). General notes: There is no file 133 due to a mistake in numbering during processing. Photographs are located in
      - Instructional assignments, 1982 - 1983; F-233-5-1-1-88 (Archival box - standard 233-60)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-339.
      - Lists of faculty members, coordinators, faculty associates, 1982 - 1983; F-233-5-1-1-89 (Archival box - standard 233-60)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-244.
      - Policies and procedures, 1982 - 1983; F-233-5-1-1-90 (Archival box - standard 233-60)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-327.
      - School district liaison - Burnaby, 1982 - 1983; F-233-5-1-1-91 (Archival box - standard 233-60)
      - Task Force on Bachelor of Education degree, 1982 - 1983; F-233-5-1-1-92 (Archival box - standard 233-60)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-93.
      - British Columbia Teachers Federation (BCTF), 1982 - 1984; F-233-5-1-1-93 (Archival box - standard 233-60)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-441.
      - Interior Conference, PDP, 1982 - 1984; F-233-5-1-1-94 (Archival box - standard 233-60)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-107.
      - Computer meetings, 1982 - 1985; F-233-5-1-1-95 (Archival box - standard 233-60)
        Informal access review completed on Feb. 24, 2022 (RM/ML): 2 documents contain personal information (employment history). 1 enclosure created for restricted material (expiry date: Nov. 21, 2084).
      - PDP and SFU open scholarships, 1982 - 1985; F-233-5-1-1-96 (Archival box - standard 233-60)
      - Fort St. John, vol. 1, 1982 - 1986; F-233-5-1-1-97 (Archival box - standard 233-67)
      - Fort St. John, vol. 2, 1982 - 1986; F-233-5-1-1-98 (Archival box - standard 233-67)
      - Fort St. John, vol. 3, 1982 - 1986; F-233-5-1-1-99 (Archival box - standard 233-67)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-302.
      - Fort St. John, vol. 4, 1982 - 1986; F-233-5-1-1-100 (Archival box - standard 233-67)
      - Fort St. John, vol. 5, 1982 - 1986; F-233-5-1-1-101 (Archival box - standard 233-67)
      - Fort St. John, vol. 6, 1982 - 1986; F-233-5-1-1-102 (Archival box - standard 233-67)
      - Trinity Western University request, 1982 - 1987; F-233-5-1-1-103 (Archival box - standard 233-67)
      - BC Research (teacher supply and demand model), 1983; F-233-5-1-1-104 (Archival box - standard 233-67)
      - Forms and procedures, 1983; F-233-5-1-1-105 (Archival box - standard 233-67)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-331.
      - Proposals for non-metropolitan programs, 1983; F-233-5-1-1-106 (Archival box - standard 233-67)
      - School district liaison - Surrey, 1983; F-233-5-1-1-107 (Archival box - standard 233-77)
      - Faculty Associate binder, vol. 1, 1983 - 1984; F-233-5-1-1-108 (Archival box - standard 233-77)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-369.
      - Faculty Associate binder, vol. 2, 1983 - 1984; F-233-5-1-1-109 (Archival box - standard 233-77)
      - Provincial Intermediate Teachers' Association (PITA), 1983 - 1984; F-233-5-1-1-110 (Archival box - standard 233-77)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-447.
      - Summer Institute in Teacher Education (SITE), 1983 - 1984; F-233-5-1-1-111 (Archival box - standard 233-77)
      - Waldorf School Association, 1983 - 1984; F-233-5-1-1-112 (Archival box - standard 233-77)
      - Strike plans, 1983 - 1987; F-233-5-1-1-113 (Archival box - standard 233-77)
      - Complaints, 1984; F-233-5-1-1-114 (Archival box - standard 233-77)
      - Interior conference, 1984; F-233-5-1-1-115 (Archival box - standard 233-77)
      - PDP promotion and school district liaison overview, 1984; F-233-5-1-1-116 (Archival box - standard 233-77)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-348.
      - Faculty Associate binder, vol. 1, 1984 - 1985; F-233-5-1-1-117 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-368.
      - Faculty Associate binder, vol. 2, 1984 - 1985; F-233-5-1-1-118 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
      - Westcast, 1984 - 1985; F-233-5-1-1-119 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-436.
      - Awards of Excellence, 1984 - 1987; F-233-5-1-1-120 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
      - Revisions to Policy AC-20: Faculty Associates and Program Coordinators in the Faculty of Education, 1984 - 1987; F-233-5-1-1-121 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
      - Academic advice in the Faculty of Education, 1985; F-233-5-1-1-122 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-363.
      - Arts, Science and Technology Centre, 1985; F-233-5-1-1-123 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
      - Educational resources - Learning Resources Centre, 1985; F-233-5-1-1-124 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
      - Jilin University, 1985; F-233-5-1-1-125 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
      - Native education, 1985; F-233-5-1-1-126 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
      - PDP interior conference, 1985; F-233-5-1-1-127 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
      - California hiring, 1985 - 1986; F-233-5-1-1-128 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
      - British Columbia Association of Math Teachers, 1986; F-233-5-1-1-129 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
      - Knowledge Network (math educational film), 1986; F-233-5-1-1-130 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
      - North Vancouver hiring procedure, 1986; F-233-5-1-1-131 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
      - Parking procedures, 1986; F-233-5-1-1-132 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
      - Peace Studies, 1986; F-233-5-1-1-134 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
      - Alaska Highway Consortium on Teacher Education (AHCOTE), vol. 1, 1986 - 1987; F-233-5-1-1-135 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
      - Alaska Highway Consortium on Teacher Education (AHCOTE), vol. 2, 1986 - 1987; F-233-5-1-1-136 (Archival box - standard 233-78)
      - Alaska Highway Consortium on Teacher Education (AHCOTE), vol. 3, 1986 - 1987; F-233-5-1-1-137 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - Award for Professional Excellence scholarship, 1986 - 1987; F-233-5-1-1-138 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - Bachelor of Education, 1986 - 1987; F-233-5-1-1-139 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - Physical Education Minor program, 1986 - 1987; F-233-5-1-1-140 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - Tri-Universities Committee, 1986 - 1987; F-233-5-1-1-141 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - Campus conferences, 1986 - 1988; F-233-5-1-1-142 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - Alert Bay, 1986 - 1989; F-233-5-1-1-143 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - Department of Mathematics and Statistics, 1986 - 1989; F-233-5-1-1-144 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - Child abuse, 1987; F-233-5-1-1-145 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - French immersion, 1987; F-233-5-1-1-146 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - Langley internship, 1987; F-233-5-1-1-147 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - Pacific French program, 1987; F-233-5-1-1-148 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - Provincial Advisory Committee on Computers (PACC), 1987; F-233-5-1-1-149 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
        Informal access review completed on Feb. 24, 2022 (ML): no restricted information identified.
      - Student retreats, 1987; F-233-5-1-1-150 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - Summer Institute in Teacher Education (SITE), 1987; F-233-5-1-1-151 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - TLC (Kelowna), 1987; F-233-5-1-1-152 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - American Educational Research Association (AERA) conference, 1987 - 1988; F-233-5-1-1-153 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - Work study / Challenge 87, 1987; F-233-5-1-1-154 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education conference, 1988; F-233-5-1-1-155 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - Teacher Development and Teacher Deployment Project, 1997; F-233-5-1-1-156 (Archival box - standard 233-79)
      - Tri-university field services and placements, 1979 - 1985; F-233-5-1-1-157 (Archival box - standard 233-58)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-309.
    - External programs year-end reports, 1974 - 1987; F-233-5-1-2; 26 cm of textual records
      Following the faculty's 1972 re-organization, it initiated a series of "external programs" designed to offer components of the PDP program from sites outside the SFU Burnaby campus. External sites included Coquitlam, Vancouver, North Vancouver, Burnaby, Surrey, Chilliwack, Kelowna, Kamloops, Penticton, Nelson, Vernon, Cranbrook, Salmon Arm, Mount Currie, Prince George, Dawson Creek, and Terrace. This sub-sub-series consists of the year-end annual reports summarizing the activities and administration of the various external programs.
      Files are arranged chronologically. Reports prior to 1981 have been grouped into files by site. From 1981-1987 reports from the various programs were bound into single volumes and are simply arranged chronologically.
      - Kelowna, 1974 - 1984; F-233-5-1-2-1 (Archival box - standard 233-62)
      - Coquitlam, 1975; F-233-5-1-2-2 (Archival box - standard 233-62)
      - North Vancouver, 1975; F-233-5-1-2-3 (Archival box - standard 233-62)
      - Salmon Arm, 1975 - 1979; F-233-5-1-2-4 (Archival box - standard 233-62)
      - Mount Currie, 1975 - 1980; F-233-5-1-2-5 (Archival box - standard 233-62)
      - Penticton, 1976 - 1980; F-233-5-1-2-6 (Archival box - standard 233-62)
      - Vernon, 1976 - 1980; F-233-5-1-2-7 (Archival box - standard 233-62)
      - Kamloops, 1976 - 1981; F-233-5-1-2-8 (Archival box - standard 233-62)
      - Prince George, 1976 - 1982; F-233-5-1-2-9 (Archival box - standard 233-62)
      - Joyce Street Program, 1977; F-233-5-1-2-10 (Archival box - standard 233-62)
      - Surrey, 1977; F-233-5-1-2-11 (Archival box - standard 233-62)
      - Vancouver, 1977; F-233-5-1-2-12 (Archival box - standard 233-63)
      - Cranbrook, 1977 - 1979; F-233-5-1-2-13 (Archival box - standard 233-63)
      - Dawson Creek, 1977 - 1979; F-233-5-1-2-14 (Archival box - standard 233-63)
      - Nelson, 1977 - 1979; F-233-5-1-2-15 (Archival box - standard 233-63)
      - Burnaby, 1977 - 1980; F-233-5-1-2-16 (Archival box - standard 233-63)
      - Chilliwack, 1977 - 1980; F-233-5-1-2-17 (Archival box - standard 233-63)
      - North Okanagan, 1977 - 1980; F-233-5-1-2-18 (Archival box - standard 233-63)
      - Terrace, 1979 - 1980; F-233-5-1-2-19 (Archival box - standard 233-63)
      - Penticton, Cranbrook, Kelowna, 1981; F-233-5-1-2-20 (Archival box - standard 233-63)
      - PDP Interior Sites Year-End Report, 1981 - 1982; F-233-5-1-2-21 (Archival box - standard 233-63)
      - PDP Interior Sites Year-End Report, 1982 - 1983; F-233-5-1-2-22 (Archival box - standard 233-63)
      - PDP Interior Sites Year-End Report, 1983 - 1984; F-233-5-1-2-23 (Archival box - standard 233-63)
      - PDP Interior Sites Year-End Report, 1984 - 1985; F-233-5-1-2-24 (Archival box - standard 233-63)
      - PDP Interior Sites Year-End Report, 1985 - 1986; F-233-5-1-2-25 (Archival box - standard 233-63)
      - PDP External Sites Year-End Report, 1986 - 1987; F-233-5-1-2-26 (Archival box - standard 233-76)
    - Reports and studies, 1969 - 1986; F-233-5-1-3; 43 cm of textual records
      Sub-sub-series consists of papers and reports relating to the SFU PDP program collected by the Faculty of Education as a library and research reference resource. The papers include Director's reports, program proposals and evaluations, studies by faculty members on various topics relating to teacher education, interviews, and consultants in-service program reports (reviewing support provided to school associates supervising PDP students in the classroom-teaching component of the program).
      - H. Branscombe: A Proposal for a Graduate Program in Professional Development, 1969; F-233-5-1-3-1 (Archival box - standard 233-80)
      - H. Branscombe:Predicting Successful Performance in the Professional Development Program at SFU, 1969; F-233-5-1-3-2 (Archival box - standard 233-80)
      - A Proposed Policy for Evaluation and Research within the Professional Development Program, [197-?]; F-233-5-1-3-3 (Archival box - standard 233-80)
      - An Evaluation Model for P.D.P., [197-?]; F-233-5-1-3-4 (Archival box - standard 233-80)
      - R.D. Gelbach: Establishing Training Objectives for Professional Students, [197-?]; F-233-5-1-3-5 (Archival box - standard 233-80)
      - A.H. Elliott: Predicting Success in Teaching, [197-?]; F-233-5-1-3-6 (Archival box - standard 233-80)
      - Director's Reports, 1973 - 1984; F-233-5-1-3-7 (Archival box - standard 233-68)
      - Faculty Associate Role Re-examined, [ca 1974]; F-233-5-1-3-8 (Archival box - standard 233-68)
      - M.R. Reed: The Faculty of Education and the School Associate -- A Shared Responsibility in Teacher Education, [ca 1974]; F-233-5-1-3-9 (Archival box - standard 233-68)
      - M.F. Wideen: Program Evaluation in Teacher Education at SFU: Some Observations, 1975; F-233-5-1-3-10 (Archival box - standard 233-68)
      - M. McClaren: External Programs and the Future of the Faculty of Education, 1975; F-233-5-1-3-11 (Archival box - standard 233-49)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-4-0-0-4.
      - Consultants' Report: Supervisory In-service Program, 1975 - 1976; F-233-5-1-3-12 (Archival box - standard 233-68)
      - G. Nelson: BC Public School System Experience by Graduates of the Professional Development Program, 1966-73, 1976; F-233-5-1-3-13 (Archival box - standard 233-68)
      - M. McClaren: Teacher In-service Education, 1976; F-233-5-1-3-14 (Archival box - standard 233-68)
      - M. Wideen and I. Allen: Delphi Study, 1976; F-233-5-1-3-15 (Archival box - standard 233-68)
      - Consultants' Report: Supervisory In-service Program, vol. 1, 1976 - 1977; F-233-5-1-3-16 (Archival box - standard 233-68)
      - Consultants' Report: Supervisory In-service Program, vol. 2, 1976 - 1977; F-233-5-1-3-17 (Archival box - standard 233-68)
      - D. Kaufman and S. Shapson: Evaluation of the Teacher Education Program at SFU, 1977; F-233-5-1-3-18 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - Field Coordinators' Report, 1977; F-233-5-1-3-19 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - J. Harper: Ideas and Information Collected During My First Semester as a Program Consultant, 1977; F-233-5-1-3-20 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - K. Pearson: Report on the Support Staff Re-organization of the Professional Development Program, 1977; F-233-5-1-3-21 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - Manpower and Staffing Needs of the Professional Development Program in 1977-78, F-233-5-1-3-22 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - Report on the Proceedings of a Colloquium for School District Personnel from the BC Lower Mainland Concerning the Professional Development Program at SFU, 1977; F-233-5-1-3-23 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - T. Cole: Alternative Learning Environments, 1977; F-233-5-1-3-24 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - Task Force on PDP Objectives, 1977; F-233-5-1-3-25 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - The Role of Faculty in In-service Education, [ca 1977]; F-233-5-1-3-26 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - PDP Summary, 1978; F-233-5-1-3-27 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - Student Teacher as a Substitute Teacher, 1978; F-233-5-1-3-28 (Archival box - standard 233-49)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-254.
      - B. Terry: Interviews of Education 405 School Associates, 1980; F-233-5-1-3-29 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - Discussion Paper on Alternate Modes of Instruction and Resource Allocation, 1980; F-233-5-1-3-30 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - Evaluation Day Comments re: PDP, 1980; F-233-5-1-3-31 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - Evaluation of the 1980 Faculty Associate Orientation, F-233-5-1-3-32 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - J. Collins: Native Indian Teacher Education Programs Needs Assessment Report, 1980; F-233-5-1-3-33 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - P. Holborn: Training School Associates in the Clinical Supervision Process, 1980; F-233-5-1-3-34 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - PDP Reports, 1980; F-233-5-1-3-35 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - School Associate Inservice Project, 1980; F-233-5-1-3-36 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - The PDP Consultant Team, 1980; F-233-5-1-3-37 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - W.O. Marble: The School Associate, 1980; F-233-5-1-3-38 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - W.O. Marble: The Supervisory Cycle, 1980; F-233-5-1-3-39 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - B. Terry: Presentation to the 1981 Westcast Conference, F-233-5-1-3-40 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - Consultants' Report: Supervisory In-service Program, 1981; F-233-5-1-3-41 (Archival box - standard 233-49)
      - D. Trainor-De Girolamo: A Report on the Delivery of Project TEACH to Education 405 Students, 1981; F-233-5-1-3-42 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - I. Andrews: Teacher Education: A Professional Model for Physical Education, 1981; F-233-5-1-3-43 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - Professional Programs Report, 1981; F-233-5-1-3-44 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - Screening Students for Teacher Education: A Pilot Project and Literature Review, 1981; F-233-5-1-3-45 (Archival box - standard 233-49)
      - W.O. Marble: A Report on the Employment Status of PDP Graduates in 1980, 1981; F-233-5-1-3-46 (Archival box - standard 233-69)
      - D. Hopkins: Enhancing the Extended Practicum, 1982; F-233-5-1-3-47 (Archival box - standard 233-76)
      - D. Trainor-De Girolamo: Faculty Associate Report, 1982; F-233-5-1-3-48 (Archival box - standard 233-76)
      - D. Trainor-De Girolamo: First Year Teacher Interviews, 1982; F-233-5-1-3-49 (Archival box - standard 233-76)
      - Dr. P.H. Winne: Research, Development, and Evaluation in PDP, 1982; F-233-5-1-3-50 (Archival box - standard 233-76)
      - C. Keddy, J. Tearne: Thirty Ills of Teacher Education, 1983; F-233-5-1-3-51 (Archival box - standard 233-76)
      - PDP year-end reports, 1983 - 1984; F-233-5-1-3-52 (Archival box - standard 233-76)
      - PDP Faculty Associate and Coordinator Year End Report, 1986; F-233-5-1-3-53 (Archival box - standard 233-76)
    - Course development files, 1970 - 1991; F-233-5-1-4; 82 cm of textual records; General note: there is no file 41 due to a mistake in numbering during processing.
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to the planning, administration, delivery, and evaluation of the course-work component of the PDP program and its modules. PDP course numbers fall in the 400 block: EDUC 401, 402, 405, 406, 407.
      Records include course descriptions, workshop and project outlines, reports, proposals, evaluations, program information, orientation handbooks, reading lists, teaching material and guides, registration procedures, student lists, schedules, forms, questionnaires, notes, working papers, and correspondence.
      For records relating to other courses (non-PDP) offered by the Faculty of Education, see the following series in this fonds:
      - F-233-6, Course files (1965-1994).
      - Education 402 - organizational / references, 1970; F-233-5-1-4-1 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-170.
      - Education 402 - organizational / references, vol. 1, 1971; F-233-5-1-4-2 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-171.
      - Education 402 - organizational / references, vol. 2, 1971; F-233-5-1-4-3 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-172.
      - Education 402 - organizational / references, 1972; F-233-5-1-4-4 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-173.
      - Education 402 - organization, 1972; F-233-5-1-4-5 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-192.
      - Education 402 - student lists, [1972?]; F-233-5-1-4-6 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-191.
      - Education 401 evaluation, 1973; F-233-5-1-4-7 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
      - Education 402 - organizational / references, 1973; F-233-5-1-4-8 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-174.
      - Suggested guidelines for Education 401 School Associates, P.D.P, 1973 - 1974; F-233-5-1-4-9 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-122.
      - Education 401/402 evaluation, M. Wideen, 1974; F-233-5-1-4-10 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-19.
      - Education 402 - organizational / references, 1974; F-233-5-1-4-11 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
      - Education 402 - organizational / references - elementary, 1974; F-233-5-1-4-12 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-175.
      - Education 402 - Organizational / references - secondary, 1974; F-233-5-1-4-13 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-176.
      - Education 402 - Problems and Possibilities, J. Ellis memo, 1974; F-233-5-1-4-14 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-74.
      - Role Distribution in the Professional Development Program - EDUC 401/402, R.D. Gehlbach, 1974; F-233-5-1-4-15 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-75.
      - Student Team Size in 401, M. Wideen, 1974; F-233-5-1-4-16 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-18.
      - A Strategy for Using the Semester Break for 401 Student Teachers who are in Secondary Schools, [ca 1975]; F-233-5-1-4-17 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-72.
      - Education 402 - organizational / references, 1975; F-233-5-1-4-18 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
      - Education 406 - organization and administration, 1975 - 1985; F-233-5-1-4-19 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-336.
      - Education 401 - Orientation Handbook, 1976; F-233-5-1-4-20 (Archival box - standard 233-53)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-4-0-0-6.